{
    "subject": "resource/Inzamam-ul-Haq",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Pakistani_Sunni_Muslims",
    "human_readable": "Inzamam-ul-Haq is a subject of Pakistani Sunni Muslims.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9870833158493042,
            "question": "Is Inzamam-ul-Haq a Pakistani Sunni Muslim?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9834362268447876,
            "question": "What is the significance of Inzamam-ul-Haq within the context of Pakistani Sunni Muslims?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7090539932250977,
            "question": "What is Inzamam-ul-Haq known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6670603156089783,
            "question": "What nationality is Inzamam-ul-Haq?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6147363781929016,
            "question": "Who are some influential figures within the Pakistani Sunni Muslim community?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5940952897071838,
            "question": "Are there other prominent Pakistani Sunni Muslims?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5840114951133728,
            "question": "To which religion do Pakistani Sunni Muslims belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3439921438694,
            "question": "How does Inzamam-ul-Haq's faith influence his life and work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34085848927497864,
            "question": "What are some key tenets of the Sunni Muslim faith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24183499813079834,
            "question": "What is the role of religion in Pakistani society?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Inzamam-ul-Haq is a subject of Pakistani Sunni Muslims.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2413_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key tenets of the Sunni Muslim faith?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2413_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does Inzamam-ul-Haq's faith influence his life and work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2413_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which religion do Pakistani Sunni Muslims belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2413_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2413_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain information that confirms Inzamam-ul-Haq's affiliation with Pakistani Sunni Muslims, as mentioned in the file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2413/re-ranker-msmarco/109.txt\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Inzamam-ul-Haq is a member of the \"Pakistani Sunni Muslims\" list, which supports the statement that he is a subject of Pakistani Sunni Muslims."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}